[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Letterboxing is usually what type of hobby?", "correct_answer": "Outdoor", "incorrect_answers": ["Indoor", "Water", "Writing"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Thomas Lennon met actress and singer Kerri Kenney at a theater camp.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 2002 movie revolves around the lives of 3 women who reach critical turning points in their lives.  The 3 women are played by Parker Posey, Kyra Sedgwick and Fairuza Balk.", "correct_answer": "Personal Velocity", "incorrect_answers": ["If These Walls Could Talk", "Singles", "Best In Show"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the occupation of Doris, one of Cinderellas ugly stepsisters in the Shrek movies?", "correct_answer": "She is a bartender.", "incorrect_answers": ["She is a karate instructor.", "She is a beautician.", "She is a nurse."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which month is celebrated as Black History Month?", "correct_answer": "February", "incorrect_answers": ["January", "April", "March"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 2005, Danny Way became the first person to do this. In the process he attained a speed of over 50 mph. What did he do?", "correct_answer": "Skateboard over the Great Wall of China", "incorrect_answers": ["Eject from an SST", "High dive from the Eiffel Tower", "Shoot out of a submarine torpedo tube"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Blue litmus paper turns red when it comes in contact with alkalines.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In general, mathematicians consider these three men to have been the greatest mathematicians of all times.", "correct_answer": "Archimedes, Newton, Gauss", "incorrect_answers": ["Newton, Gauss, Einstein", "Newton, Gauss, Euler", "Archimedes, Newton, Einstein"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Approximately how many pencils are sold annually in the USA?", "correct_answer": "2,000,000,000", "incorrect_answers": ["500,000,000", "200,000,000", "20,000,000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does Professor Julius Kelp transform into in the 1963 comedy movie The Nutty Professor?", "correct_answer": "A smooth womanizer", "incorrect_answers": ["A voluptuous woman", "A dog", "A hamster"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "John Larroquette has  won many acting awards. How many CONSECUTIVE Emmys did he  win ?", "correct_answer": "4", "incorrect_answers": ["5", "6", "3"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "John Travolta played Vincent Vega in Pulp Fiction, but Tarantino wanted to cast another actor in the role.  This actor turned down the part in order to appear in Wyatt Earp. Who is the actor?", "correct_answer": "Michael Madsen", "incorrect_answers": ["Sylvester Stallone", "Nicolas Cage", "Harvy Keitel"]}]